[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mom always told you to get plenty of iron in your diet, so you order a put out the lights and cry.  What item have you ordered?", "correct_answer": "Liver and onions", "incorrect_answers": ["Patty melt, no onions", "Ham on rye with soup", "T - Bone steak with onions"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For their size hippos are pretty fast runners and are much faster than humans.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the oldest  symphony  orchestra  in the USA?", "correct_answer": "The New York Philharmonic", "incorrect_answers": ["The Symphony Orchestra of New   Orleans", "The Boston Philharmonic", "The Philadelphia  Philharmonic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the U.S. National Weather Service, after you see and hear the last flash of lightning and roar of thunder, you should wait how long before presuming outdoor activities?", "correct_answer": "30 minutes", "incorrect_answers": ["1 hour", "2 hours", "10 minutes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Amathophobia is an irrational fear of what?", "correct_answer": "dust particles", "incorrect_answers": ["thunder  lightning", "movement or change", "falling in love"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrays God in the movie Bruce Almighty?", "correct_answer": "Morgan Freeman", "incorrect_answers": ["Philip Baker Hall", "Denzel Washington", "Laurence Fishburne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The terms ahimsa and satyagraha  are generally associated with whom?", "correct_answer": "Mahatma Gandhi", "incorrect_answers": ["Angelina Jolie", "Buddha", "Indira Gandhi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What would be the Earth like without evaporation?", "correct_answer": "Warmer", "incorrect_answers": ["Cooler", "None of these", "Greener"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Was the iPod launched on October 23, 2001?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of creature was the extinct Plesiosaur, which is usually said to be similar to the monster of Loch Ness?", "correct_answer": "Mesozoic reptile", "incorrect_answers": ["Dinosaur", "Humanoid", "Fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete the words, said by nurse Wilkins in the movie Grease: Its the first day of school and already my ........................ is missing.", "correct_answer": "castor oil", "incorrect_answers": ["thermometer", "band aids", "cigarettes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal cures asthma, arteriosclerosis, impotence, thyroid problems, broken bones, and heart disease according to traditional Chinese medicine?", "correct_answer": "Seahorse", "incorrect_answers": ["Snake", "Shark", "Frog"]}]